LARRY SKARSET

3458 Bonita Avenue, Santa Clara, CA 95051 • Home: 408 500 5359 • Cell: 408 500 5359 • lskarset@aol.com

Professional Summary

I have been in financial services for many years I understand products and understand peoples concerns and problems

Skills

excellent communication skills

Series 7 63 66 and Insurance license Enrolled in American college for financial planning

Work History

Registered Represenative, 02/2012 to Current LifeMark Securities – Rochester, NY sales and working with clients

Registered Representaive, 02/2010 to 02/2012 FSC Securities – Walnut Creek, CA

Registered representative , 03/1992 to 05/2010 Western International Securities – San Jose, CA

Owner operator, 01/1969 to 03/2015 Self employed Barber – Palo Alto, CA

Education

Associate of Arts: Finance, 1971 Foothill college - Los Altos Hills, CA

Certifications

Life Insurance license securities licenses 7 63 66